I'm going to buy something.
سأذهب لشراء بعض الأشياء
It's dirty inside. I haven't cleaned up yet.
في الداخل متسخ ولم أنظف
It's okay.
لا بأس
Go inside and watch the film.
اذهب إلى غرفتك لترى الفيلم
I'll take it to you
عندما أنتهي
when I'm done.
سأرسلها لك
I want to see you cook.
أريد أن أراك تطبخ
I've never seen it before. I'm curious.
لم أر من قبل   فضولي
You are curious about everything.
أنت فضولي في كل شيء
Wait a minute.
انتظري
I'll clean up.
سأقوم بالترتيب
I've bought you some barbecue.
اشتريت لك الشواء
Eat it yourself.
اذهب لتناول الطعام بنفسك
Okay, got it.
حسنا فهمت
It's so spicy.
حار جدا
Do you want some?
هل تريد أن تترك لك القليل
No, I don't like it.
لا، لا أحب هذا
I just finished it.
لقد انتهيت من الأكل
In what way do you want to cook?
ماذا تريد أن تفعل
What do you want to eat?
كيف تريد أن تأكل
Egg them before deep-frying.
‫ضع البيض في المقلي‬
Don't you think it's troublesome?
لا تكره المتاعب
It isn't me doing it anyway.
على أي حال لست أنا من فعلها
You're here.
أنا قادم
Wait in the room.
اذهب إلى الداخل وانتظر
No.
لا
I just want to watch you work here.
أريد فقط أن أراك تعمل هنا
The workshop is too cold.
المصنع بارد جدا
No need to wipe.
لا داعي
I'll wash it myself.
سأغسل بنفسي بعد قليل
I'm leaving first. Hurry up.
‫سأذهب بسرعة‬
I didn't mean it.
لم أقصد ذلك
I just want to see the ending.
أريد فقط أن أرى النهاية
Get ready to eat.
أرتب وتناول الطعام
Don't watch these anymore.
لا تنظر إلى هذه الأشياء فيما بعد
You should study hard.
أدرس بجد
I didn't know they'd have the scene.
لا أعرف أنني سأؤدي هذا
Remember to call me.
تذكر أن تتصل بي
Last semester,
في الفصل الماضي
you had underperformance.
أدائك سيئ للغاية
I often couldn't contact you.
لا يمكنني العثور على أحد.
There was a lot of training
التدريب كثير
and only a few training places with a strong signal.
هناك القليل من الاشارة.
I know.
أعرف
Call me
على أي حال أنت لست مشغولا
whenever you are unoccupied.
اتصل بي
You are...
أنت
Has your first love
هل عاد
back yet?
هل عدت؟
I want to see him.
أريد أن أرى
Probably no.
لا
What do you mean by probably no?
ماذا تعني لا؟
Haven't you asked him?
لم تسأل
The kid is with you.
لقد وضعت طفلك هنا
Shouldn't you two
إذًا
chat three times a day?
يجب أن تحياتا ثلاث مرات في اليوم
He has a special occupation.
مهنته مميزة
Sometimes, he disappears for a few days.
لم أره منذ عدة أيام
How can I chat with him always?
كيف يمكن أن يقال في الوقت المحدد
And if he comes back,
وإذا عاد
I think he will inform me.
سيعود
Long time no see.
لم أرك منذ وقت طويل
You're still the same.
لا تزال كالمعتاد
Nothing good happens when I see you.
لا شيء جيد عندما أراك
You're in your thirties,
أكثر من ثلاثين سنة
but still, act like a teenager.
لا تزال مثل العشر من عمرها
Is it fun?
هل هذا ممتع
You're back.
لقد عدت
Minshan, you are here.
مين شان أنت هنا
Aunt.
عمتي
Come here.
تعال تعال
Come and sit here.
اجلسي هنا
How did you get here?
كيف أتيت
My dad sent me here.
أرسلني أبي
Where is your dad?
ماذا عن والدك؟
He has a dinner party tonight.
لديه العشاء الليلة
So he didn't have time
ليس لدينا وقت
to visit you.
جئت لألقي التحية عليك
No need.
لا داعي لا داعي
He doesn't have to bother visiting me.
لا داعي لتقديم التحية لي
Lu Chen, get Minshan a glass of water.
‫لو تشين، أحضر لي كوبا من الماء من مين شان
Mum, I'm leaving.
أمي سأذهب
Sister will be here soon.
ستأتي أختي بعد قليل
I'm talking to you.
أنا أتحدث معك
Aunt.
خالتي
He came to accompany you overnight
لقد نزل من القطار
after getting off the train.
لذلك أتى لمرافقتك طوال الليل
Let him go back and rest early.
دعه يرجع ويسترح مبكرًا
Speak it out.
لنتحدث
What's your relationship
ما علاقتك
with Zhao Minshan?
تشاو مين شان؟
Could you even be together at such a far distance?
كيف يمكن أن يلصق بك بعد المسافة
I don't think so.
لا أعتقد ذلك
I'm a little tired.
أنا متعب قليلا
I don't want to talk.
لا أريد التحدث
I heard that
سمعت
Zhao Minshan had just divorced not more than two years.
تشاو مين شان لم يطلق منذ عامين
Be careful.
كن حذراً
She is
إنها
very scheming.
لديها عقل عميق
She screwed me up.
لقد خدعتني في البداية
You disappointed Meng Xiaoshan
لم تستطع تحمل الإغراء
because you couldn't stand the temptation.
‫فأشعر بالأسف تجاه منغ شياو شان‬
Yes, you're right.
نعم أنت على حق
I can't blame others.
لا ألوم الآخرين
It's my fault.
ألوم نفسي
You're back.
لقد عاد
Uncle Liu is dirty.
العم ليو متسخ
I've accustomed to it when I was young.
اعتدت على ذلك عندما كنت صغيرة
Okay.
حسنا
Let's go out and eat.
هيا لنخرج لتناول الطعام
Everybody is going together.
‫اذهبوا جميعاً
It's on Uncle Liu's treat today.
العم ليو على حسابه اليوم
Haidong, let's go together.
هاي دونغ، لنذهب معاً
Okay, Uncle Liu.
حسناً يا عم ليو
Let's go.
لنذهب
Is everything good in Qining?
جيد في تشي نينغ
Are you coming back for getting married?
هل ستتزوج هذه المرة
Who is he marrying?
من هو
Could it be
هل هو
his girlfriend who's in Qining?
حبيبة تشي نينغ
You didn't even tell me.
لم تخبرني
I'm not planning to get married.
لم تنوي الزواج
Will your dad allow you
هل يمكن لوالدك أن يسامحك
not listening to him?
أنت لا تستمع إليه
What happened exactly?
ماذا حدث؟
Who can let me in on it?
‫من قال لي
It's Lu Chen's father.
‫هو والد لو تشين لاو لو
He'd borrowed more than one million
‫قبل بعد
from the Zhao family
اقترضت أكثر من مليون من عائلة تشاو
and couldn't pay it back.
ولم أتمكن من سدادها
Later, the daughter of the Zhao family
بعد ذلك ابنة عائلة تشاو
said,
قالت
"How about this?
ما رأيك بهذا؟
We can become in-laws.
أن نتزوج
You don't have to pay back the money."
لا تسدد هذا المال
The daughter also said,
‫قالت الابنة مرة أخرى
"Lu Chen and I
‫أنا لو تشين
are old classmates.
‫نحن زملاء قديمين
We know each other well.
نحن أصدقاء
I'm willing to marry him."
أنا مستعد للزواج منه
Zhao Minshan?
تشاو مين شان
Did you also hear about it?
لقد سمعت أيضاً
I figured it out.
‫خمنت ذلك
But Lu Chen,
‫لكن لو تشين
now,
‫الآن
you don't have to be afraid of your dad.
لا داعي للخوف من والدك
He's old now.
إنه كبير في السن الآن
Maybe
ربما
he won't be able to punish you anymore.
لا يمكنه أن يتحرك
But you can't
لكن هذا الحساب
welch on the debt.
لا يمكن إنكاره
You are his son.
أنت ابنه
If you don't pay his debt,
إذا لم تدفع ديونه
he will force your elder sister to pay it back.
سيجبر أختك على سداد الدين
Am I right?
أليس كذلك؟
Enough.
حسنا حسنا
Lu Chen just came back.
ألم يعد لو تشين للتو؟
Let's talk about something cheerful.
لنتحدث عن شيء سعيد
Come on.
هيا
Okay.
حسنا
Let's eat.
لنأكل
There's always a solution.
هناك دائما طريقة لحل المشكلة
Qin Xiaonan.
تشين شياو نان
Just put your clothes there.
ضعي الملابس هناك
I'll wash them together later.
سأغسلها معا
No, I'll do it myself.
لا حاجة سأغسلها بنفسي
Do you like washing clothes so much?
أنت تحب غسل الملابس
Then help me
ساعدني
wash mine too.
اغسلي لي أيضا
Just kidding.
أمزح معك
It's okay.
لا بأس
Take your clothes to me.
أعطني إياه
I'll wash them for you.
سأساعدك في غسلها
I don't dare to slave you.
لا أجرؤ على خدمتك
I'm serious. Just put them there.
أنا أقول الحقيقة ضعها هناك
If you
إذا
feel sorry to trouble me,
أنا آسف لإزعاجك
I'll wash them
سأعود
with a washing machine.
سأستخدم جهاز الغسيل لك
It can be dried too. How awesome it is!
من الجيد أن تجففها
I'm on a business trip the day after tomorrow.
سأذهب للعمل بعد غد
I may not be able to
ربما لا أستطيع
take care of Qin Xiaonan.
لرعاية تشين شياو نان
Come pick him up if you have come back.
إذا كنتِ ستعودين فلتأتي لاستقباله
If not...
إذا لم تعد بعد
Who should take care of him?
من سيكون من الأفضل أن يعتني به
It's usually not a big deal.
لا بأس
But now the Chinese New Year is around the corner.
إنه عيد الربيع
It's inappropriate to place him at anyone's house.
ليس من المناسب أن أضعه في أي منزل
We'll see.
لنتحدث
Speak it out.
قل
What have you been doing recently?
ماذا تفعل مؤخرا
After the class reunion,
بعد حفلة الزملاء
we have no chance to hang out with you at all.
لم أره
I'm working.
أعمل
What else can I do?
ماذا يمكنني أن أفعل
I got something to share with you.
أريد أن أخبرك بشيء
I heard that
سمعت للتو
Zhao Minshan,
تشاو مين شان
who had divorced two years ago...
ألم نتطلق قبل عامين؟
It was a hearsay, Gui Xiao.
سمعت أن "جاي شياو"
I heard that
‫سمعت
Chen had just returned
‫تشين عاد
two days ago.
‫قبل يومين؟
They are getting married.
إنهما مشغولان
Who?
‫من؟
Chen.
‫تشين
I remember when Chen came back last time,
‫عندما عاد تشين
So I'm telling you the news.
‫لذا جئت لأخبرك
Is Lu Chen back?
‫لقد عاد لو تشين
♫My unbosoming no longer attracts you♫
‫نعم
He came back yesterday.
لقد عدت بالأمس
I didn't expect
لم أتوقع
our campus beau to be
ساحر مدرستنا الثانوية
obtained by Zhao Minshan.
من قبل تشاو مين شان
Also,
وأيضاً
the Zhao family is ready for a wedding.
عائلة تشاو مستعدة لإقامة حفل زفاف
They have booked the restaurant
فندق محدد
managed by Meng Xiaoshan.
هي منغ شياو شان
Aren't you familiar with Meng Xiaoshan?
‫ألا تعرف منغ شياو شان جيدا‬
Ask her.
اسأليها
She must know better than me.
يجب أن تعرف أكثر مني
I have to go.
لا أتحدث معك الآن
♫But the situation has come to a head♫
لنتحدث لاحقا
Okay, bye.
حسنا مع السلامة
Happy New Year in advance.
‫سنة سعيدة مقدما
Happy New Year.
سنة سعيدة
I heard you went back to Beijing.
سمعت أنك عدت إلى بكين
He just asked me to do him a favour.
طلب مني أن أفعل شيئا فقط
I agreed and it's already done.
لقد وافقت
It should be over.
حان وقت الانتهاء
Don't give it too much thought.
لا تفكري كثيرا
He didn't say anything.
لم يقل أي شيء
Hello?
ألو
Sorry, Gui Xiao.
أنا آسف، لقد عدت
Something urgent came up at home.
هناك أمر طارئ في المنزل هذه المرة
I'm back for two days.
عدت ليومين
But I had a busy schedule.
لا يمكنني الخروج
It's okay.
لا بأس
I'm leaving Beijing the day after tomorrow.
سأغادر بكين بعد غد
The Chinese New Year is coming.
اقترب عيد الربيع
It's not suitable
ليس من المناسب
to leave the kid to my friends.
اطلب من الأصدقاء أن يعملوا الأطفال
I heard you were back.
سمعت أنك عدت
So I wanted to ask you when you will be free
فأريد أن أسألك متى
to pick up the kid.
تعال لاستقبال الطفل
The day after tomorrow.
بعد غد
How about I just drive him there?
ما رأيك أن أقود السيارة إلى هنا
I'll go tomorrow.
سآتي غدا
It's a deal.
اتفقنا
Thank you.
شكرا لك
No problem.
لا بأس
I can help you.
‫يمكنني مساعدتك
Lu Chen.
‫لو تشين
I'm saving money.
‫أنا أجمع المال
I'll visit you when I have enough money.
سأذهب لرؤيتك عندما أجمع ما يكفي
One more minute, okay?
‫هل يمكنك التحدث دقيقة أخرى؟
Do you miss me?
هل اشتقت إلي؟
Can't you say more?
ألا يمكنك قول المزيد؟
Don't we
نحن
speak the same language?
لا يوجد لغة مشتركة
I'm now living on campus.
أنا في المدرسة
I'm so torn.
أنا مترددة للغاية
There are four people in our dorm.
‫يوجد أربعة أشخاص في سكننا‬
I don't know if I can get used to it.
لا أعرف إذا كان بإمكاني أن أعتاد عليه
Oh no.
يا إلهي
My mum knows who you are.
أمي تعرف من أنت
Recently,
مؤخرا
I can't answer the phone at home.
لا يمكنني الرد على الهاتف
Don't call me.
لا تتصل بي
Wait for my call.
‫انتظر حتى أتصل بك
Lu Chen.
‫لو تشين
Bye.
‫سأغلق الخط
It's winter.
في الشتاء
Why didn't you close the door and block the wind?
لماذا لا تغلق الباب وتمنع الرياح
Why are your eyes red?
لماذا عيناك حمراء
Did you quarrel with your dad?
هل تشاجرت مع والدك؟
No.
لا
I recall the past.
تذكرت الماضي
The past?
الماضي
Isn't your past all about Gui Xiao?
أليس ماضيك هو عودتك
What could you recall?
ماذا تذكرت؟
Why did you break up?
لماذا انفصلتما
I still haven't figured it out yet.
لم أفهم حتى الآن
Look, when I broke up with Meng Xiaoshan,
انظري انفصلت عن منغ شياو شان
it's my fault.
هذا خطأي
What about you two?
ماذا عنكما؟
It's my fault.
اللوم علي
At that time,
في ذلك الوقت
she was a girl.
إنها فتاة
She put all her emotions
تضع كل المشاعر
on the phone call.
على خط الهاتف
She couldn't see or touch them.
لا يمكن رؤيتها ولا يمكن لمسها
How pitiful.
كم هو مسكين
Actually, during that period,
في الواقع في ذلك الوقت
when I couldn't see her,
لم أراها
I missed her too.
أشتاق إليها أيضا
I missed her so much.
‫أفتقدها كثيراً
Every time I hear her calling me Lu Chen,
‫في كل مرة أسمعها تناديني لو تشين
and calling my name on the phone,
‫تناديني باسمي على الهاتف
I feel that she has the most pleasant voice
أعتقد أن هذا هو
in the world.
في العالم
Every time.
كل مرة
Enough. Stop it.
يكفي يكفي يكفي
You make me feel sad.
أشعر بالأسف
Normally,
في السن العادي
she should have gotten married.
يجب أن يتزوج
Her children should be teens ages.
كم عمر الطفل
Where are you going?
إلى أين تذهب
Take a shower.
الاستحمام
Shower? It's Chinese New Year.
‫الاستحمام في مهرجان الربيع
There's no heater in your bathroom.
ليس لديك حمام دافئ
Do you want to be frozen to death?
‫هل تريد التبريد حتى الموت
I've even taken a bath in the snow in Qining.
لقد غسلت في حمام الماء في تشي نينغ شيوه
I'm not afraid of the cold.
‫لا أخاف من البرد
I'll fix the car.
سأذهب لإصلاح السيارة
He dismantles the car
هذا الفتى
every time he feels sad.
إذا حزينا فتهدم السيارة
It never changes.
لن يتغير أبدا
I came here with only one bag of stuff.
‫عندما جئت كيس من الأشياء‬
But I'm leaving with this much.
لقد مشيت كثيرا
My dad will scold me.
سيوبخ أبي
Not much at all.
ليس كثيرًا
These are
هذه كلها
for you to wear
ما تستخدمه في المدرسة فيما بعد
in school later.
كمية الملابس
You're going to see Uncle Lu soon.
‫سنلتقي العم لو
Are you happy?
هل أنت سعيد
Yes.
نعم
I wonder if the repair shop
لا أعرف إن كان مصنع الصيانة
is still accommodable.
هل يمكن السكن فيه
What a waste.
هذا مضيعة
These slippers are so small.
هذا النعال صغير جدا
Who will wear them in the future?
من سترتديه في المستقبل
Little wordy. Let's go.
يا لك من ثرثار، لنذهب
Here.
تعال
Aunt Gui Xiao, is this the place?
العمة جو شياو هل هذا هو
We're here.
وصلنا
So spacious!
كبير جدا
It's larger than I thought.
‫أكبر مما تخيلت
Hello, I'm looking for Lu Chen.
‫مرحباً أنا أبحث عن لو تشين
Wait, miss.
‫انتظري يا فتاة
I'll make a call.
سأتصل بالداخل
It's cold outside. Come in first.
الجو بارد في الخارج ادخل أولا
Come on, kid.
‫تعال الطفل أيضا‬
Okay, thank you.
حسنا شكرا
Let's go.
‫هيا بنا
Someone is looking for Lu Chen. At the door.
‫هناك شخص يبحث عن لو تشين عند الباب
A girl and a kid.
‫فتاة وطفل
Miss, he'll come out now.
‫يا فتاة اخرجي حالاً
Does this factory all belong to Uncle Lu?
‫هذا المصنع من العم لو
Yes.
‫نعم كلهم
Uncle Lu.
‫العم لو
Is it new-bought?
‫اشتريتها جديدة
He had too much stuff to fit.
‫كان لديه الكثير من الأشياء لا يمكن وضعها‬
So I bought him a new one.
اشتريت واحدة جديدة
I won't go in further.
لن أدخل
Come.
تعال
Come inside and have a seat.
ادخل واجلس
Where is the toilet?
أين المرحاض
The right side.
يمين
It's cold in the factory.
‫المصنع بارد‬
Don't take off your coat first.
لا تستعجل في خلع معطفك
I'll leave after a few words.
سأذهب بعد أن أشرح لك بضع كلمات
I've found a private school
مدرسة تشين شياو نان الخاصة
for Qin Xiaonan.
تم العثور عليه
I'll be away for a long time.
كنت في رحلة عمل لفترة طويلة
But I'll ask my cousin
لكن سأطلب من ابن عمي
to take you to school.
أن يأخذكم إلى المدرسة
I bought some clothes for him.
اشتريت له بعض الملابس
From now on,
في المستقبل
you should also buy him some clothes every year.
سأشتري له بعض الملابس كل عام
But not too many.
لكن لا حاجة إلى الكثير
He can wear school uniforms usually.
في العادة يوجد الزي المدرسي
That's all.
هذا كل شيء
Do you still love me?
هل ما زلت تحبني؟
Bai Chao said that
قال باي تشاو
you were getting married.
أنك ستتزوج
Lu Chen?
‫لو تشين
Yes.
‫نعم
When?
متى
Next month.
الشهر القادم
Congratulations.
تهانينا
Aunt.
‫خالتي
Uncle Lu is getting married.
‫العم لو سيتزوج
He'll be quite busy.
‫سيكون مشغولاً
Remember
ما قلته لك في السيارة
what I told you in the car.
يجب أن تفكري بنفسك
Also,
وأيضا
if you are neglected at school,
إذا تم تجاهلها في المدرسة
remember what Aunt Gui Xiao said.
تذكر ما قالته العمة جو شياو
All transfer students
الطلاب المتنقلون
will go through this process.
ستواجهون هذه العملية
They'll accept you after a long time.
سوف يقبلوك بعد فترة طويلة
Aunt.
عمتي
Go on with your work. I'm leaving.
استمري في عملك سأذهب
Wait.
انتظر
How much is the suitcase?
كم سعر الصندوق
Here's for Xiaonan's clothes
ملابس نان
and his living cost of staying at your house for days.
وأيضًا هذه الأيام التي تعيش فيها في منزلك
Thank you.
‫شكراً
Lu Chen.
‫لو تشين
You don't have to be so calculative.
‫لا تحتاج إلى الحساب بوضوح
You helped me in Qining.
‫لقد ساعدتني في تشي نينغ
Lu Chen.
‫لو تشين
Why are you not coming out? There're guests outside.
‫لم يخرج حتى لو ناديتك
You...
أنت
You are...
أنت أنت
Gui Xiao.
"غوي شياو"
Do you still remember me?
هل تتذكرني؟
I'm Zhao Minshan from Class 2.
تشاو مين شان من الصف الثاني
Long time no see. You've been prettier.
‏لم أرك منذ وقت طويل، تبدين جميلة‏
I nearly
لقد
couldn't recognize you.
كدت لا أعرفها
Are you
‫أنت
the friend Lu Chen's mother mentioned?
‫صديقة قالت والدة لو تشين
I heard from Mrs Lu that
‫سمعت من والدة لو
he had a friend coming today.
أن لديه صديق سيأتي اليوم
Since he has been outside
كنت أفكر أنه كان في الخارج
all these years,
طوال هذه السنوات
I've never seen
لم أر هؤلاء الأصدقاء
those of his friends.
لم أرهم من قبل
So I came out
لذلك أريد الخروج
to have a look.
ألقي نظرة
I didn't expect that it was you.
لم أتوقع أن تكون أنت
What a coincidence.
يا لها من صدفة
Is this your kid?
طفلك
It's his comrade's.
صديقه
He asked me to go through the school procedure for him.
‫طلب مني أن أقرر الدراسة
Lu Chen never mentioned it.
‫لم أسمع لو تشين يذكر
I've sent the kid here.
‫لقد أرسل الطفل
I'm leaving first.
سأغادر
Please don't go.
لا تذهب
Stay here and have lunch with us.
‫ابق لتناول الغداء معاً
Oh, Lu Chen.
‫لو تشين أنت حقاً
She came through a far way.
‫لقد جاءت من بعيد
How could you not invite her for a meal?
لماذا لا تبقيها لتناول الطعام
No need.
لا داعي لا داعي
I have an appointment with Meng Xiaoshan.
لدي موعد مع منغ شياو شان
Meng Xiaoshan?
‫منغ شياو شان‬
Forget it, then.
انسي الأمر
Girl.
يا ابنتي
Why are you leaving now?
ماذا؟ هل ستغادر الآن؟
I knew you were coming.
أعلم أنك ستأتي اليوم
So I went to buy fish for you.
ذهبت لشراء السمك لك
We'll see.
لنتحدث
Thank you.
شكرا لك
Girl, you...
يا ابنتي أنت
Why don't you eat first before you leave?
ما رأيك أن نذهب بعد الأكل
Enough.
توقف عن الكلام
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Are you hurt?
هل تأذيت؟
I'm fine.
أنا بخير
It's really broken here.
لقد كسرت هنا
Just repair it here.
اصلحها هنا
Anyone? Come over here.
هناك شخص بالداخل
Take the job.
‫حان وقت العمل‬
No need.
لا داعي لا داعي
I can fix it myself.
سأصلحها بنفسي
You can fix it here.
من الجيد إصلاحها هنا
No need.
لا داعي
Excuse me.
من فضلك افسح الطريق
I have to reverse out.
سأسحب السيارة
Thank you.
شكرا لك
There's no heater in your room.
ليس لديك حمام دافئ في غرفتك
Your suitcase is expensive.
صندوقك ليس رخيصًا
Your parents are so willing to
والداك
spend money on you.
أنت حقاً على استعداد لدفع المال لك
You have no conscience.
ليس لديك ضمير
Go and do your homework.
‏اذهبوا إلى الواجبات‏
Waive the bill for that table.
لا داعي لهذا الطاولة
Apologize properly.
اعتذر جيدًا
Hello, Gui Xiao.
مرحباً جوى شياو
I'm hungry.
أنا جائع
Go to the lobby.
اذهب إلى القاعة بسرعة
I need to take this call.
أجيب على الهاتف
Gui Xiao, you sound like something's wrong.
جوى شياو هذا الصوت غير صحيح
Did something happen at your home?
حدث شيء في المنزل
Do you need money?
هل تريد اقتراض المال
I'll send it to you.
سأرسلها لك
No.
لا
I'm just hungry.
أنا فقط جائعة
I haven't eaten since morning.
لم أتناول الطعام منذ الصباح حتى الآن
I was just passing by,
لقد مررت من هنا
and I thought of
تذكرت أنك قلت
you mentioned buying me a meal.
أن تدعوني لتناول الطعام
Where are you?
أين أنت
By the river.
نقل النهر
Which entrance?
‫أي مدخل
The intersection
‫خارج مصنع لو تشين
outside Lu Chen's factory.
‫ذلك التقاطع الصغير
Are you here to pick me up?
لتأخذني
What are you doing? Put me down.
ماذا تفعل أنزلني
I have something urgent to do.
هناك أمر طارئ علي الذهاب
How old are you?
كم عمرك
Aren't you afraid of hurting your back?
ألا تخشى أن يلمس خصرك
Did you cry?
هل بكيت؟
No.
لا
I just feel
فقط
a little down.
‫غير مريح
Because of Lu Chen, right?
‫من أجل لو تشين
You two always came here for dating.
‫أنتما دائماً تأتين إلى هنا في موعد
Don't think I've forgotten.
لا تعتقد أنني نسيت
Let me take a guess.
دعني أخمن
You are upset
أنت من أجل
because of
بشأن تشاو مين شان و لو تشين
Lu Chen and Zhao Minshan.
هل تشعرين بعدم الارتياح؟
Everyone knows
بشأن طلاق تشاو مين شان
about Zhao Minshan's divorce.
الجيران يعرفون
She was embarrassed and anxious to get married again.
أن العائلة محرجة وتريد الزواج الثاني
But after years of hard efforts,
لقد عملت بجد لعدة سنوات
none of them can impress her.
لا أحد يستطيع أن يلاحقها
Finally,
‫أخيراً جاء
Lu Chen has fallen into her lap.
‫لو تشين
So, a few days ago,
‫لذلك منذ بضعة أيام
since she got engaged to Lu Chen,
‫منذ الخطوبة مع عائلة لو تشين
and received the betrothal gifts,
‫بعد قبول العروس
she was desperate to hold a grand banquet
أريد أن أقيم النبيذ على الفور
immediately.
لنبدأ
She has invited all her acquaintances in the neighbourhood.
لقد دعوت جميع المألوفين
You. How old are you?
أنت كم عمرك
Still crying for your first love who has been ten years ago?
ما زلت تبكين من أجل الحب الأول قبل عشر سنوات
Don't blame me for scolding you, Gui Xiao.
لا تلومني على توبيخك
You thought you were still 18.
ظننت أنني في الثامنة عشر من عمري
There are many things you don't know.
لا تعرف الكثير
When I told Haidong to break up,
لقد أخبرت هاي دونغ في البداية
we made it clean in the end.
ألم يتم قطعها؟
You should have cried enough
يجب أن تبكي
when you broke up.
لقد بكيت عندما انفصلت
Everyone has a first love.
من ليس لديه الحب الأول
If you keep thinking about your first love,
إذا كنت تفكر في الحب الأول دائما
how are you supposed to move on?
هل ستعيش الحياة في المستقبل
I'm hungry.
أنا جائع
Okay, let's eat something delicious.
حسنا سآخذك لتناول الطعام الجيد
The most delicious one.
الأفضل
Give me the car key.
أعطني مفتاح السيارة
Where's your car?
أين سيارتك
We're all acquaintances around here.
‫جميع المعارف في هذا المكان‬
I'm not afraid of losing it.
لا تخاف من فقدها
I'll ask my husband
دع زوجي يأتي بعد قليل
to drive it back.
وأعيده
It feels good.
شعورك جيد
I can switch with you if you want.
إذا أردت القيادة فسأغير السيارة معك
No need.
لا داعي
You're already dying.
لا يزال لديك حياة أو موت
How can I profit from your misfortunes?
كيف يمكنني الاستفادة من النار
Who's dying?
من يريد أن يموت